Guide to the Cornell University Office of Alumni Affairs. Regional club records, 1911-2008.
Cornell University Office of Alumni Affairs. Regional club records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Office of Alumni Affairs. Regional club records, 1911-2008.
41-6-635
Cornell University. Office of Alumni Affairs.
38.1 Cubic Feet.
Correspondence, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence and records of the Alumni Office and its regional clubs
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence and records of the Alumni Office and its regional clubs; include records of Cornell Day celebration also correspondence (1911-1918) concerning the Advisor of Women's position originally held by Mrs.Gertrude S. Martin, including letters from Mrs. Martin and women in various Cornell Clubs to President Schurman expressing their concern that the position was not a faculty one.
Also 5 films from Southwest Regional Office. Various Cornell buttons from the Northeast Regional Office.
Also 12 Cornell buttons.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Martin, Gertrude S.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Cornell University--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Includes collection #41-6-1492.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box lists for other boxes are not online.
- Committee reports to Board of Directors, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Scripts for slide shows, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Cornell Women's Club of New York City, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Cornell Club of New York, 1966-1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Cornell Clubs of Penn-York and Ontario County, 1960-1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Cornell Women's Club of Rochester, 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Cornell Club of Rochester, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Cornell Club of Rockland County, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Cornell Women's Club of Schenectady, 1962-1966 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Cornell Club of Schenectady, 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Cornell Club of Schenectady, 1957-02-20 and undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  Includes constitution and bylaws
- Cornell Clubs of Skaneateles, Staten Island, Suffolk and Sullivan Counties, 1962-1968 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Cornell Women's Club of Syracuse, 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Cornell Women's Club of Westchester County, 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Cornell Women's Club of Westchester County, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Cornell Club of Westchester, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Cornell Men's Club and Cornell Women's Club Combined of Schenectady, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  Includes proposed constitution and bylaws
- Cornell Club of Wyoming County, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Photographs and programs from various alumni associations around the country, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Guide for Cornell Clubs, 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Event planning and club organization, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Club organization, presidential dinners, program planning and publicity and attendance, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Guide to Cornell Clubs and Alumni Associations, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  Fall
- Guide to Cornell Clubs and Alumni Associations, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Guide to Cornell Clubs and Alumni Associations, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Regional Director's Guide to Cornell Clubs, Undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Cornellians and Cornell, 1974-09-20; tr-16041 (Box 24)
- Thanks to You slide sound show with Joe Leeming and Frank Rhodes, 1981-01-16; tr-16042 (Box 24)
- Facetime Alumni Song, 1982; tr-16043 (Box 24)
- Reunion and various other Cornell buttons, 1966-1999 (Box 24)
- Arizona-Southern, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Arizona-Southern, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- California-Los Angeles, 2002-2005 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- California-Los Angeles, 2000-2002 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- California-Los Angeles, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Alumni Directory, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Connecticut-Fairfield County, 2000-2003 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Connecticut-Fairfield County, 1996-2000 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Connecticut-Fairfield County, 1989-1996 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Florida-Eastern, 2000-2003 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Florida-Eastern, 1996-2000 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Florida-Eastern, 1989-1995 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Florida-Eastern-Membership Directory, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Florida-Sarasota-Manatee, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Florida-Sarasota-Manatee, 1994-1998 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Florida-Sarasota-Manatee, 1989-1994 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Georgia-Atlanta, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Georgia-Atlanta, 1989-1996 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Illinois-Chicago, 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- New York-Ithaca, 1998-2003 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Massachusetts-Boston, 1999-2002 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Massachusetts-Boston, 1997-1999 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Massachusetts-Boston, 1995-1997 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Massachusetts-Cape Cod, 1997-1999 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Massachusetts-Cape Cod, 1989-1997 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Ohio-Northeastern, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Ohio-Northeastern, 1992-1994 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Ohio-Northeastern, 1989-1991 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Zinck's, 1988-1998 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Zinck's, 1984-1991 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Alaska Club, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Austin Club, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Austin Club, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Austin Club, 2000-2002 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Austin Club, 1984-2000 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Houston Club, 1999-2001 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Houston Club, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Houston Club, 1989-1996 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- London Club, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- The London Club, 2000-2003 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- The London Club, 1992-2000 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- North Texas, 2000-2003 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- North Texas, 1989-2000 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Alumni Celebration, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- 125th Anniversary-Clubs Celebrations, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Vietnam/Korea Memorial, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Zinck's, 1997-2003 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Cornell Club of Tucson, 1962-03-06 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Cornell Women's Club of Norther California, 1963-01 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  Includes constitution
- Cornell Club of the Gold Coast, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
  Includes mailings, photos, attendees list, etc.
- Cornell Club of the Gold Coast, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 7-8)
- Cornell Club of the New Haven, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Cornell Club of Maricopa County, Undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  Constitution
- Cornell Club of Soutwest Florida, 1972-02 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Cornell Club of Sarasota-Manatee, 2011-2012 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  Includes board and committee book
- Cornell Club of Lackawanna, New Jersey, Undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Cornell Club of Essex Conty, New Jersey, Undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Cornell Club of Trenton, New Jersey, 1941-11-05 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Cornell Women's Club of Central New Jersey, 1947-10-23 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Cornell Women's Club of Elmira, New York, Undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Cornell Alumni Association of Central New York, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Cornell Women's Club of Greater Cincinnati, 1960-01-26 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Cornell Club of Northwestern Pennsylvania, 1958-05-15 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Cornell Women's Club of Milwaukee, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Cornell Club of Milwaukee, 1962-02 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Cornell Piedmont Alumni Club, 1969-02 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs, 1970-07-13 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Annual Reports
  - Annual Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Annual Reports, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Annual Reports, 2007-2008 (Box 42, Folder 21)